<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>NetSys Research Group UPB</title><link>http://example.org/</link><description>Recent content on NetSys Research Group UPB</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>http://example.org/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/contact/</guid><description>You can find us in Room 203, Precis Building. You can also contact us by emailing Costin</description></item><item><title/><link>http://example.org/members/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/members/</guid><description>Faculty Costin Raiciu - networking, systems Dragos Niculescu - wireless, localization, networking Marios Choudary - security, side-channel attacks Lorina Negreanu - formal methods, verification Matei Popovici - formal methods, verification Current students Dragos Dumitrescu (PhD) Vladimir Oleanu (PhD) Costin Lupu (PhD) Radu Stoenescu (PhD) Mihai-Valentin Dumitru (PhD) Laura Flueratorul (PhD) Vlad-Andrei Badoiu (PhD) Mihai-Drosi Caju (PhD)</description></item><item><title/><link>http://example.org/open-positions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/open-positions/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>http://example.org/publications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/publications/</guid><description>2021 Unikraft: Fast, Specialized Unikernels the Easy Way - Simon Kuenzer, Vlad Badoiu, Hugo Lefeuvre, Sharan Santhanam, Alex Jung, Gaulthier Gain, Cyril Soldani, Costin Lupu, Stefan Teodorescu, Costi Raducanu, Cristian Banu, Laurent Mathy, Razvan Deaconescu, Costin Raiciu, Felipe Huici - in Eurosys 2021 [PDF; Video] [Awarded Best Paper]
FlexOS: Making OS Isolation Flexible - Hugo Lefeuvre, Vlad Badoiu, Stefan Teodorescu, Pierre Olivier, Tiberiu Mosnoi, Razvan Deaconescu, Felipe Huici, Costin Raiciu - in HotOS 2021 [PDF; Video]</description></item><item><title/><link>http://example.org/research/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/research/</guid><description>The NETSYS research group focuses on networking and systems research. Its expertise in networking is best seen in the two protocols it has helped design, implement and test: Multipath TCP and NDP. In the broader systems area, the group is working on virtualization (see LightVM paper in SOSP 2017), security (see CHES 2017 paper) and network verification (see Sigcomm 2016).
Current Projects Unikraft Dataplane verification EQDS</description></item><item><title/><link>http://example.org/student-projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/student-projects/</guid><description>Looking for Bachelor or Master projects, or a Master thesis? Below are some project ideas.
Unikraft related projects Unikraft is a novel a novel micro-library OS that (1) fully modularizes OS primitives so that it is easy to customize the unikernel and include only relevant components and (2) exposes a set of composable, performance-oriented APIs in order to make it easy for developers to obtain high performance.
Your own idea Do you have a project idea related to Netsys’s interests?</description></item></channel></rss>